

IRTIFA ZABIN

Address: House: 48, Road: 7/B, Block:H, Banani, Dhaka

Phone: +8801790051562

Filone. +0001790031302

E-mail: irtifa_zabin@yahoo.com

OBJECTIVE

"Keeping my eyes on the stars, and feet on the ground"

Self-motivated professional with +4 years of HR and administrative experience in multi-national; manufacturing and consulting firms. Now, seeking a human resource position in a reputable and fast paced organization where my excellent planning and management skills will be fully utilized.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Big Fish Hunter Executive Search

Mar 2021 — May 2021

Executive Search Consultant

- 1. Partner with customers to get a clear view on their strategic and financial objectives and hiring needs.
- 2. Research into clients company, competitors and market place.
- 3. Map role criteria, define position description and document specifications.
- 4. Identifying and recruiting prospective candidates using a variety of channels.
- 5. Assessing candidates to ensure qualification match, cultural fit and compatibility.
- 6. Conducting confidential interviews and checking references.
- 7. Present shortlisted candidates and provide detailed profile summaries.
- 8. Offer guidance and facilitate the negotiation process through to its completion.
- 9. Follow up with clients and assist with the candidate's transition and onboarding process.
- 10. Trainings: Mapping; Resume Recognition.

Decathlon Sports, Bangladesh

July 2016 — Dec 2020

HR & Office In-Charge

- 1. Managing a team of four (POC for Decathlon Chittagong Office).
- 2. Serving as resource steward for HR and Finance leader. Overseeing factors such as office/ event budgets, expense forms and petty cash.
- 3. Recruiting and screening potential candidates.
- 4. Delivering friendly assistance with new hires throughout interviewing and hiring process.
- 5. Managed quality assurance program, including on-site evaluation; office audits and employee surveys.
- 6. Coordinating office activities and improving operations to secure efficiency and compliance as company policies Continuous Improvement (CI Mindset) Office.
- 7. Arranging travel itineraries (incoming+outgoing) for local and foreign colleagues.
- 8. IT relay.
- 9. Trainings: Negotiation; Basic Supply Chain; Supply Methods; CI; Recruitment; Communication; Managing Suppliers; Time Management & Prioritizing and more.

Irtifa Zahin

Lanka-Bangla Securities; Motijheel Branch

HR Intern

Manning Global AG, Munich

Mar 2013 — May 2013

May 2015 — July 2015

Finance Assistant

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts: Business Studies Oct 2011 — July 2014

Globe Business College Munich, Germany

Result: HND - Merit Grade Bachelor - 2:1

Research Project: To assess the impact of non-ethical behavior on leasing real-estate by foreigners in Bangladesh.

IELTS

British Council

Overall Band - 7.0

German Language Course

Die Sprache

Level - A1

O-Level & A-Level

Chittagong Grammar School/ British Council

Subject: Science (O-level) | A,A,B,C,E,E Business (A-level) | C,C

INTERESTS

- Playing any kind of sports (preferred: Football; Basketball; Table Tennis; Swimming)
- Fitness
- Hiking/ Trekking
- Technology
- Music
- Sustainable Development/ Continuous Improvement

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTS

- Permanent member of Chittagong Club Limited.
- Diversity Programme (The American Chamber of Commerce AmCham).
- Industrial visits to:
 - ~ Schedl Automotive System GmbH & Co. KG | Leipzig, Germany.
 - ~ The Bid | London, UK.
 - ~ Finow Automotive GmbH | Berlin, Germany.
 - ~ Audi Forum | Ingolstadt, Germany.
 - ~ Autohaus Hornung | Garmisch-Patenkirchen, Germany
 - ~ Merck Finck & Co.
 - ~ Ed Meier | Munich, Germany

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

Irtifa Zabin